JOSEPH E. PERSICO PAPERS (APAP030) 1910-2003
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
1975 January 16 Washington, D.C., Draft, Briefing Presidential Appointment
1975 January 16 Washington, D.C., Draft, Governors and Mayors
1975 January 23 Washington, D.C., Draft, Nuclear Energy Regulatory Commissioners
1975 January 26 New York City, NY, Radio TV Reports, Face the Nation
1975 January 28 Washington, D.C., Draft, Wildlife Fund
1975 January 28 Washington, D.C., Draft, Washington Press Club
1975 January 28 Washington, D.C., Address, To US Congress
1975 January 29 Milburn, NJ, Press conference, New Jersey Republican Finance Dinner Vietnam
1975 January 29 Milburn, NJ, Draft, New Jersey Republican Finance Dinner Vietnam
1975 February 4 Washington, D.C., Draft, US Travel
1975 February 6 Washington, D.C., Press Briefing, after Meeting Gov. Carey and Mayor Beane
1975 February 13 New York City, NY, Excerpts of Remarks, Salute to Vice President
1975 February 13 Washington, D.C., Draft, Salute to Vice President
1975 February 26 Detroit, MI, Excerpts of Remarks, Energy
1975 March 7 Washington, D.C., Remarks to Press, Q and A
1975 March 22 Washington, D.C., Draft, Gridiron Dinner
1975 July 10 Washington, D.C., Remarks, Conference of Mayors
1975 August 5 Washington, D.C., Remarks, Meeting with Summer Intern
1975 August 5 Washington DC, Remarks, World Conference on the Deaf
1975 August 5 Washington DC, Press Release, Health, Education, and Welfare
1975 August 26 Mobile, AL, Excerpts of Remarks, National Conference of Lt. Governors
1975 August 26 Mobile, AL, Remarks, National Conference of Lt. Governors
1975 August 26 Mobile, AL, Press Conference, National Conference of Lt. Governors
1975 August 27 Columbia, SC, Remarks, at Lace House
1975 August 27 Columbia, SC, Press Conference and Q and A Session
1975 August 27 Columbia, SC, Remarks, G.O.P. Reception
1975 August 27 Columbia, SC, Press Conference and Q and A
1975 August 28 New York City, NY, Opening Statement, before Moreland Act Commission
1975 August 28 New York City, NY, Speech, Moreland Act Commission on Nursing Homes
1975 September 5 Rochester, NY, Remarks, Monroe County Kick off
1975 September 5 Rochester, NY, Remarks, Highland Hospital
1975 September 5 Rochester, NY, Remarks, Holler Medical Center
1975 September 5 Rochester, NY, Press Conference, Q and A Session
1975 September 5 Greece, NY, Remarks, Dedication of Park Ridge Hospital
1975 September 5 Greece, NY, Dedication of Park Ridge Hospital
1975 September 5 Rochester, NY, Chairman's Club Reception
1975 September 5 Washington, D.C., Remarks, of President Ford
1975 September 12 Dallas, TX, Remarks, Republican Women's Convention
1975 September 12 Dallas, TX, Remarks, 10:50 AM Republican Women's Convention
1975 September 12 Dallas, TX, Remarks, Multi Station TV Taping
1975 September 12 Dallas, TX, Press Conference, Q and A Session
1975 September 12 Little Rock, AR, Remarks, Testimonial regarding Winthrop Rockefeller
1975 September 12 Morrilton, AR, Press Release, Testimonial regarding Winthrop Rockefeller
1975 September 12 Morrilton, AR, Remarks, Testimonial regarding Winthrop Rockefeller
1975 September 13 Oklahoma City, OK, Press Conference, Tinker Air Force Base
1975 September 13 Norman, OK, Remarks, at Reception of Jack Black
1975 September 13 Enid, OK, Remarks, Vance Air Force Base
1975 September 13 Enid, OK, Press Conference, Oakwood County Club
1975 September 13 Enid, OK, Remarks, Garfield County Fare Grounds
1975 September 13 Enid, OK, Remarks, Republican Fund Raising Dinner
1975 September 15 London, England, Remarks, Rockefeller at US Bicentennial
1975 September 17 Washington, D.C., Remarks, Reading is Fundamental
1975 September 18 Washington, D.C., Remarks, National Medal of Science
1975 September 24 Washington, D.C., Draft, Presentation of Public Occurrences
1975 September 29 Washington, D.C., Federal City Council
1975 September 29 Washington, D.C., Draft, Federal City Council
1975 October 2 Washington, D.C., Remarks, Conference on Energy
1975 October 3 Portland, OR, Press Conference, Q and A Hilton Hotel
1975 October 3 Portland, OR, Western State Republican Conference Dinner
1975 October 3 Portland, OR, Remarks, Western State Republican Conference Dinner
1975 October 6 Washington, D.C., Remarks, Energy Conference
1975 October 7 Kings Mt., NC, Remarks, Bicentennial Celebration
1975 October 7 Kings Mt., NC, John H. Gamble Stadium
1975 October 8 Washington, D.C., Press Release, Roundtable on Private Committee
1975 October 9 Washington, D.C., Briefing, Roundtable on Private Committee
1975 October 11 Newport, VA, Remarks, Eisenhower Ship Launching
1975 October 11 New York City, NY, Remarks, Annual Columbus Day Dinner
1975 October 15 Columbus, OH, Press Conference, at Columbus Sheraton
1975 October 15 Columbus, OH, Remarks, at Columbus Sheraton
1975 October 16 Charleston, W. VA, Press Conference, West Virginia State House
1975 October 16 Charleston, W. VA, GOP Reception
1975 October 16 Roanoke, VA, at Hotel Roanoke
1975 October 16 Roanoke, VA, Remarks, General GOP Reception
1975 October 21 Denver, CO, Remarks, Public Forum on Domestic Policy
1975 October 21 Denver, CO, Press Conference, Public Forum on Domestic Policy
1975 October 23 Indianapolis, IN, Press Conference, Indianapolis Convention Center
1975 October 23 Indianapolis, IN, Indiana Republican State Convention
1975 October 23 Indianapolis, IN, TV Taping, with J. Linksey WLWI-TV
1975 October 23 Indianapolis, IN, Remarks, Indiana State Teachers Association
1975 October 23 Decatur, IL, Remarks, Macon County Republican Committee
1975 October 24 Milwaukee, WI, TV Taping, with John McCollough WTJM-TV
1975 October 24 Milwaukee, WI, Press Conference, Pfister Hotel
1975 October 24 Milwaukee, WI, United Negro College Fund
1975 October 29 Tampa, FL, Press Conference, Tampa Convention Center
1975 October 29 Tampa FL, Remarks, Public Forum on Domestic Policy
1975 October 31 New York City, NY, Press Release, Hebrew Union College
1975 November 2 ABC News, Issues & Answers
1975 November 3 Washington, D.C., Press Release, Letter to President
1975 November 10 Air Force Two, Press Conference, Q and A Session
1975 November 10 Austin, TX, Remarks, Conference on Public Life
1975 November 11 Austin, TX, Remarks, Public Forum on Domestic Policy
1975 November 11 Austin, TX, Press Conference, Q and A Session
1975 November 14 Kansas City, MO, Remarks, Future Farmers of America
1975 November 14 Kansas City, MO, Future Farmers of America
1975 November 14 Kansas City, MO, Press Conference, Future Farmers of America
1975 November 14 Lincolnshire, IL, Press Conference, McClary Testimonial Dinner
1975 November 14 Lincolnshire, IL, Remarks, McClary Testimonial Dinner
1975 November 15 Minneapolis, MN, Remarks, Metropolitan College Club
1975 November 15 Minneapolis, MN, Q and A, Metropolitan College Club
1975 November 15 St. Cloud, MN, Minnesota Republican Convention
1975 November 15 St. Cloud, MN, Minnesota Republican Convention
1975 November 15 St. Cloud, MN, Press Conference, of Vice President St. Cloud
1975 November 15 St. Paul, MN, Remarks, Elephant Club Reception
1975 November 15 St. Paul, MN, 76 Spirit Bicentennial
1975 November 18 Philadelphia, PA, Public Forum on Domestic Policy
1975 November 18 Philadelphia, PA, Press Conference, Benjamin Franklin Hotel
1975 November 19 Washington, D.C., Remarks, Council of 100 Dinner
1975 November 19 Washington, D.C., Remarks, Representive Congress
1975 November 20 Wichita, KS, Press Conference, McConnel Air Force Base
1975 November 20 Wichita, KS, State GOP Reception
1975 November 21 Wichita, KS, Q & A Session, Republican Governors Conference
1975 November 21 Wichita, KS, Republican Governors Conference
1975 December 3 New York City, NY, Statement, Moreland Act Commission on the Urban Development Corporation
1975 December 4 Pittsburgh, PA, Republican Awards Dinner
1975 December 4 Pittsburgh, PA, Press Conference, Q and A at Hilton Hotel
1975 December 5 New York City, NY, Remarks, National Association of Manufacturers
1975 December 9 Los Angeles, CA, Los Angeles Convention Center
1975 December 9 Los Angeles, CA, Press Conference, Los Angeles Convention Center
1975 December 10 Washington, D.C., Remarks, Council on the Environment
1975 December 11 Nashville, TN, Press Conference, Metro Center
1975 December 11 Nashville, TN, Remarks, Republican State Committee
1975 December 11 Houston, TX, Informal Remarks, Black Republican Leaders
1975 December 11 Houston, TX, Black Republican Leaders
1975 December 11 Houston, TX, Houston Business Man Club
1975 December 11 Houston, TX, Press Conference, Hyatt Regency
1975 December 12 Houston, TX, TV Taping, KTRK-TV
1975 December 12 Houston, TX, Remarks, Southern Republican Council
1975 December 17 Washington, D.C., Press Conference, Briefing Room
1976
1976 January 14 Washington, D.C., Remarks, National Council of Farmers
1976 January 14 Washington, D.C., National Council of Farmers
1976 January 19 Washington, D.C., Remarks, 2nd Session of 94th Congress
1976 January 20 Washington, D.C., Statement, Water Quality Hearing
1976 January 26 Washington, D.C., Remarks, Bolling Air Force Base
1976 January 26 Salem, WV, Remarks, Salem College Convocation
1976 January 26 Salem, WV, Salem College Convocation
1976 January 29 Rye, NY, Remarks, Westchester County Republican Committee
1976 January 30 Rye, NY, Excerpts, Westchester County Republican Committee
1976 January 30 Dearborn, MI, Press Conference, Q and A Dearborn Hyatt
1976 January 30 Dearborn, MI, Remarks, Republican Reception
1976 January 30 Dearborn, MI, Toast by Rockefeller, to Governor and Mrs. Milliken
1976 January 31 Dearborn, MI, Excerpts of Remarks, Mid-West Republican Leadership
1976 February 3 Washington, D.C., Press Conference, White House Briefing Room
1976 February 4 Washington, D.C., Remarks, Senate Committee of Government Operations
1976 February 6 Washington, D.C., Remarks, National Council of the Arts
1976 February 10 Washington, D.C., Remarks, Atomic Industry Forum Conference
1976 February 10 Washington, D.C., Remarks, 1:10 PM Atomic Industry Forum Conference
1976 February 12 Louisville, KY, Remarks, Republican Lincoln Day Memorial
1976 February 12 Louisville, KY, Remarks, Kentucky State Republican Galt House
1976 February 12 Louisville, KY, TV Taping, WAVE TV Galt House
1976 February 12 Louisville, KY, Press Conference, Galt House Hotel
1976 February 12 Louisville, KY, TV Taping, Excerpt of Interview Campaign 1964
1976 February 12 Louisville, KY, Excerpt of Interview
1976 February 14 New York City, NY, Remarks, New York Republican County Committee
1976 February 15 New York City, NY, Excerpts of Remarks, New York Republican County Committee
1976 February 19 Washington, D.C., Summary, Press Club
1976 February 19 Washington, D.C., Text of Remarks, Press Club
1976 February 19 Washington, D.C., Press Club
1976 February 19 Washington, D.C., Excerpt of Speech, Press Club Campaign 1964
1976 February 20 Lansing, MI, Remarks, Michigan State Republican Committee
1976 February 20 Lansing, MI, Press Conference, Holiday Inn
1976 February 20 Lansing, MI, Michigan State Republican Committee
1976 February 23 Boston, MA, Remarks, American Association for Advancement of Science
1976 February 24 Washington, D.C., Remarks, National Governors Conference
1976 February 24 Washington, D.C., Summary, National Governors Conference
1976 February 25 Philadelphia, PA, Remarks, Bicentennial Bishops
1976 February 25 Philadelphia, PA, Bicentennial Bishops
1976 March 9 New York City, NY, Remarks, Religion in American Life
1976 March 9 New York City, NY, Summary, Religion in American Life
1976 March 10 Washington, D.C., Remarks, National Industrial Energy Council
1976 March 10 Washington, D.C., Press Release, National Industrial Energy Council
1976 March 12 Albuquerque, NM, Press Conference, Albuquerque Convention Center
1976 March 12 Albuquerque, NM, Lincoln Day Dinner
1976 March 12 Albuquerque, NM, Remarks, Lincoln Day Dinner
1976 March 16 Chicago, IL, Remarks, National American Wholesale Grocery
1976 March 16 Chicago, IL, Summary, National American Wholesale Grocery
1976 March 17 Chicago, IL, Press Conference, Crystal Room Palmer House
1976 March 17 Chicago, IL, Executive Club of Chicago
1976 March 17 Chicago, IL, Summary, Executive Club of Chicago
1976 March 18 Washington, D.C., Excerpts of Remarks, Joint Economic Committee
1976 March 19 Washington, D.C., Press Release, off of Ticket as Vice President
1976 March 22 Paris, France, Draft, Lafayette Tomb
1976 March 22 Paris, France, Draft, Draft, Our Common Heritage
1976 April 6 Washington, D.C., Draft, Lyndon B. Johnson Memorial Grove
1976 April 7 Reston, VA, Summary, Energy Leadership Conference
1976 April 7 Reston, VA, Remarks, Energy Leadership Conference
1976 April 8 Arlington, VA, TV Taping, Robert McNul Report
1976 April 12 Washington, D.C., Statement, Energy Independence Authority
1976 April 12 Washington, D.C., Press Release, Energy Independence Authority
1976 April 12 Philadelphia, PA, President Ford Committee
1976 April 12 Philadelphia, PA, Summary, The Need to Grow
1976 April 12 Philadelphia, PA, Remarks, Club of Rome Banquet
1976 April 14 Des Moines, IO, Press Conference, Des Moines Airport
1976 April 14 Des Moines, IO, Remarks, Lincoln Day Dinner
1976 April 14 Des Moines, IO, Lincoln Day Dinner
1976 April 15 Atlanta, GA, Peachtree Plaza
1976 April 15 Atlanta, GA, Press Conference, Peachtree Plaza
1976 April 20 Washington, D.C., Remarks, President's Commission on Personnel Interchange
1976 April 20 Washington, D.C., President's Commission on Personnel Interchange
1976 April 28 Washington, D.C., Remarks, Oceanic Organization
1976 April 28 Washington, D.C., Remarks, Annual Neptune Award
1976 April 29 Washington, D.C., Remarks, National Leadership Conference
1976 April 29 Washington, D.C., Summary, America's Health Policy
1976 April 30 Washington, D.C., Remarks, George Washington Monument
1976 April 30 Washington, D.C., George Washington Monument
1976 May 4 San Francisco, CA, Press Conference, 11:35 AM Fairmont Hotel
1976 May 4 San Francisco, CA, Summary, Commonwealth Club of California
1976 May 4 San Francisco, CA, Commonwealth Club of California
1976 May 5 Los Angeles, CA, Summary, World Affairs Council
1976 May 5 Los Angeles, CA, Press Conference, World Affairs Council
1976 May 5 Los Angeles, CA, World Affairs Council
1976 May 7 Queens, NY, Remarks, Queens County Republican Dinner
1976 May 10 Philadelphia, PA, Remarks, 9:20 AM International Press Institute
1976 May 10 Philadelphia, PA, Remarks, PM International Press Institute
1976 May 15 Germany, Remarks, Bicentennial Speech
1976 May 19 Yorktown, VA, Draft of Speech, Ceremony
1976 May 19 Yorktown, VA, Text of Remarks, Ceremony
1976 May 20 Cincinnati, OH, Press Release, President Ford Committee
1976 May 20 Cincinnati, OH, President Ford Committee
1976 May 23 Newport, RI, Remarks, Touro Synagogue
1976 May 24 Newport, RI, Text of Remarks, Touro Synagogue
1976 May 26 Washington, D.C., Remarks, Conference, on Regulatory Reform
1976 May 26 Washington, D.C., on Regulatory Reform
1976 June 2 Colorado Springs, CO, Air Force Academy
1976 June 2 Colorado Springs, CO, Press Release, Air Force Academy
1976 June 4 Ocean City, MD, Maryland Republican Convention
1976 June 4 Ocean City, MD, Press Conference, Maryland Republican Convention
1976 June 4 Ocean City, MD, Press Release, Maryland Republican Convention
1976 June 9 Washington, D.C., Draft of Speech, Broadcast Editors Association
1976 June 9 Washington, D.C., Broadcast Editors Association
1976 June 9 Washington, D.C., Press Release, Broadcast Editors Association
1976 June 16 Washington, D.C., Press Release, Old Senate Chamber
1976 June 16 Washington, D.C., Press Release, National Hearing Conference
1976 June 16 Washington, D.C., National Hearing Conference
1976 June 17 New York City, NY, New York State Republican Dinner
1976 June 18 Greensboro, NC, Press Conference, Four Seasons Holiday Inn
1976 June 18 Greensboro, NC, Press Release, Four Seasons Holiday Inn
1976 June 18 Greensboro, NC, Press Release, Republican Reception
1976 June 21 West Orange, NJ, Press Conference, Town and Campus Motor Inn
1976 June 21 West Orange, NJ, Town and Campus Motor Inn
1976 June 22 Washington, D.C., Press Release, American Hebrew University
1976 June 22 Washington, D.C., American Hebrew University
1976 June 24 Hauppauge, NY, Press Conference, Colonie Hill Restaurant
1976 June 24 Hauppauge, NY, Nassau County Republicans
1976 June 30 Washington, D.C., Paul Findley Award
1976 July 1 Washington, D.C., Text of Remarks, Chartbook Ceremony UNIVAC I
1976 July 1 Washington, D.C., Chartbook Ceremony UNIVAC I
1976 July 2 Washington, D.C., Draft, National Archives
1976 July 2 Washington, D.C., Text of Remarks, National Archives
1976 July 2 Washington, D.C., Press Release, Tribute to Freedom
1976 July 4 Washington, D.C., Text of Remarks, Pageant of Freedom
1976 July 4 Washington, D.C., Pageant of Freedom
1976 July 8 Washington, D.C., Press Release, Toast to Queen Elizabeth II
1976 July 15 Washington, D.C., Text of Remarks, Albert Einstein Spacearium
1976 July 15 Washington, D.C., Press Release, Albert Einstein Spacearium
1976 July 19 Wilmington, DE, Press Conference, Hotel Dupont
1976 July 19 Claymont, DE, 1976 Victory Kick off
1976 July 22 Washington, D.C., Address, to 94th Congress Ford
1976 July 29 Washington, D.C., Republican Hispanic Assembly
1976 August 2 Bar Harbor, ME, Press Conference, Trenton Airport Bar Harbor
1976 August 2 Seal Harbor, ME, Press Conference, Rockefeller and Richard Rosenbaun
1976 August 4 Washington, D.C., Text of Toast, Finland's President Kekkonen
1976 August 5 Washington, D.C., Text of Toast, Finland's President Kekkonen Dinner
1976 August 9 Kansas City, MO, Statement, Republican Platform Committee
1976 August 9 Kansas City, MO, Remarks, Committee on Resolutions
1976 August 9 Kansas City, MO, Press Conference, Municipal Auditorium
1976 August 16 Kansas City, MO, Press Release, Republican Convention
1976 August 16 Kansas City, MO, Address, Kemper Arena
1976 August 19 Kansas City, MO, Kemper Arena
1976 August 19 Kansas City, MO, Text of Address, Republican Convention
1976 August 19 Kansas City, MO, Remarks, Republican National Convention
1976 September 14 Washington, D.C., Questions and Answers
1976 September 15 Buffalo, NY, Press Release, Local Republican Reception
1976 September 16 Buffalo, NY, Press Release, Ford-Dole Campaign
1976 September 16 Buffalo, NY, Ford-Dole Campaign
1976 September 16 Buffalo, NY, Press Conference, 9:30 AM, Ford-Dole Campaign
1976 September 16 Rochester, NY, Ford-Dole Campaign
1976 September 16 Rochester, NY, Press Conference, 11:39 AM, Ford-Dole Campaign
1976 September 16 Syracuse, NY, Ford-Dole Campaign
1976 September 16 Syracuse, NY, Press Conference, 1:10 PM, Ford-Dole Campaign
1976 September 16 Binghamton, NY, Ford-Dole Campaign
1976 September 16 Binghamton, NY, Press Conference, 3:10 PM, Ford-Dole Campaign
1976 September 16 New York City, NY, Ford-Dole Campaign
1976 September 16 New York City, NY, Press Conference, Rockefeller and Senator Bob Dole
1976 September 21 Chicago, IL, Press Conference, Conrad Hilton Hotel
1976 September 21 Chicago, IL, TV Taping, Conrad Hilton Hotel
1976 September 21 Chicago, IL, Thompson Grand Ballroom
1976 September 21 Chicago, IL, Thompson International
1976 September 22 Chicago, IL, Press Release, Fall Campaign
1976 September 22 Cleveland, OH, Press Conference, Bond Court Hotel
1976 September 22 Cleveland, OH, Ford Committee Headquarters
1976 September 22 Cleveland, OH, Cuyahoga County Republicans
1976 September 22 Cleveland, OH, TV Taping, Studio 1 TV5
1976 September 22 Cleveland, OH, TV Taping, Studio 2 TV5
1976 September 22 Columbus, OH, Columbus Bar Association
1976 September 22 Columbus, OH, Press Conference, Fort Hayes Hotel
1976 September 22 Columbus, OH, TV Taping, Fort Hayes Hotel
1976 September 22 Cincinnati, OH, Press Conference, Cincinnati Airport
1976 September 22 Cincinnati, OH, TV Taping, Parlor C Cincinnati Club
1976 September 22 Cincinnati, OH, TV Taping, 3rd Floor Cincinnati Club
1976 September 22 Cincinnati, OH, Harrison Room Cincinnati Club
1976 September 22 Washington, D.C., Press Release, Ohio Campaign
1976 September 28 Hasbrouck, NJ, Sheraton Heights Hotel
1976 September 28 Dover, NJ, Press Conference, 12:12 PM, Three Sisters Restaurante
1976 September 28 Dover, NJ, Morris County Republicans
1976 September 28 Philadelphia, PA, Distinguished Republicans
1976 September 28 Philadelphia, PA, Press Release, Distinguished Republicans
1976 September 28 Philadelphia, PA, TV Interview, WCAU-TV
1976 September 28 Philadelphia, PA, TV Taping, Mike Douglas Show
1976 September 28 Philadelphia, PA, Press Conference, Holiday Inn
1976 September 29 Erie, PA, Ciro's Restaurant
1976 September 29 Erie, PA, Press Conference, Holiday Inn
1976 September 29 Erie, PA, TV Taping, WICU-TV
1976 September 29 Pittsburg, PA, Text of Remarks, Republican Support Committee
1976 September 29 Pittsburg, PA, Republican Support Committee
1976 September 29 Pittsburg, PA, Press Conference, Hilton Hotel
1976 September 29 Pittsburg, PA, TV Taping, KDKA-TV
1976 September 29 Pittsburg, PA, Press Ford Committee
1976 October 5 London, England, Draft, North American Indian Art
1976 October 5 London, England, Press Release, The Hayward Gallery
1976 October 7 Chicago, IL, Press Conference, Hilton Hotel
1976 October 7 Chicago, IL, Grand Ballroom Hilton
1976 October 7 Chicago, IL, Salute to President
1976 October 7 Chicago, IL, Text of Remarks, Salute to President
1976 October 9 New York City, NY, Draft, Columbus Citizens Committee
1976 October 9 New York City, NY, Columbus Citizens Committee
1976 October 9 New York City, NY, New York County Republicans
1976 October 9 New York City, NY, Ukrainian American Congress
1976 October 12 New York City, NY, Remarks, Salute to President Ford
1976 October 13 New York City, NY, Press Release, Salute to President Ford
1976 October 13 San Francisco, CA, TV Interview, KOG- TV
1976 October 13 San Francisco, CA, Press Conference, St. Francis Hotel
1976 October 13 San Francisco, CA, TV Interview, KNXT-TV
1976 October 13 San Francisco, CA, Text of Remarks, Golden Circle Club
1976 October 13 San Francisco, CA, Press Release, Golden Circle Club
1976 October 13 Sacramento, CA, TV Interview, KCRA-TV
1976 October 13 Portland, OR, Press Conference, Air National Hangar
1976 October 13 Portland, OR, TV Interview, KOIN-TV
1976 October 13 Portland, OR, TV Interview, KGW-TV M. White
1976 October 13 Portland, OR, Hilton Hotel
1976 October 13 Portland, OR, V.I.P. Reception
1976 October 14 Seattle, WA, Text of Remarks, J. Spellman Volunteers
1976 October 14 Seattle, WA, Press Release, J. Spellman Volunteers
1976 October 14 Seattle, WA, J. Spellman Volunteers Fund Raiser
1976 October 14 Seattle, WA, Press Conference, Olympic Hotel
1976 October 14 Everett, WA, Remarks, J. N. Garner Rally
1976 October 18 Kalamazoo, MI, Press Conference, 10:40 AM, Airport Terminal
1976 October 18 Kalamazoo, MI, Republican Fund Raising
1976 October 18 Grand Rapids, MI, Press Conference, 12:35 PM, Kent County Airport
1976 October 18 Grand Rapids, MI, Lunch with Rocky
1976 October 18 Saguran, MI, Press Conference, Tri-City Airport
1976 October 18 Saguran, MI, Denton Marvin Fund Raising
1976 October 18 Detroit, MI, Press Conference, Ponchartrain Hotel
1976 October 18 Detroit, MI, TV Taping, WWJ-TV
1976 October 18 Detroit, MI, Press Release, Cobo Hall
1976 October 18 Detroit, MI, Young Republican Reception
1976 October 18 Detroit, MI, Michigan Republicans
1976 October 19 Bloomington, MN, Press Conference, Registry Hotel
1976 October 19 Bloomington, MN, Candidate Reception
1976 October 19 Bloomington, MN, TV Taping, Henry Wolf Show
1976 October 19 Minneapolis, MN, Press Release, Elephant Club
1976 October 19 Bloomington, MN, Elephant Club
1976 October 19 Bloomington, MN, Normandale Community College